<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Home</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Throughout my career, I have worked in many different positions and sectors to contribute positive business results by performing another level of prioritization to increase productivity. The experience that I have gained over the years, allows me to understand people easily and communicate with them in an effective way. While I’m independently motivated, I do appreciate collective efforts and collaborate productively within group settings.
Music I love discovering new tracks trough Soundcloud and in the Blog section you may find some cool ones to chill or dance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact/</guid>
      <description>Follow me, @johndoe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Exchange Rate Volatility and Tourism in Turkey</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description>The paper has written during the last semestre of my senior year as a graduation thesis. The topic itself is deeply related to my previous experiences and the the data that has been used can be found the link below.
(https://evds2.tcmb.gov.tr)
Abstract This paper investigates the relationship between the average expenditure per tourist which is calculated as total travel incomes divided by the total number of departing visitors, the exchange rate and inflation of package holidays by using OLS method.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>